(Sheldon:)I can't believe
you're not on my side.
(Sheldon:)I was on your side when someone
stole your car radio.
(Amy:)Who else's side
could you have been on?
(Howard:)I don't know.
(Sheldon:)A music-loving hobo
with a heart of gold?
(Amy:)Sheldon, I understand
that you're upset
(Amy:)because you feel left out,
(Amy:)but I don't know why
we're even talking about this.
(Amy:)Just apologize to them.
(Sheldon:)Fine, if that's what it takes
to go on their dumb trip.
(Amy:)Maybe you could try apologizing
because you actually feel bad.
(Amy:)It's called empathy.
(Amy:)It's something
you could work on.
(Sheldon:)I have empathy.
(Penny:)Watch.
(Sheldon:)Leonard made me soup,
and I was mean to him.
(Emily:)Great.
(Amy:)Now try it as if this isn't
your first day as a person.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)Leonard made me soup,
and I was mean to him.
(Sheldon:)Hey, I felt a little something.
(Sheldon:)Let me try again.